izlemex.org 2018-10-18

# None

**Privacy Policy PDF All Designers Ebooks** , PDF All Designers Ebooks is committed to user privacy and/or our policy below and describes our principles in maintaining user trust and confidence and protecting your private data. PDF All Designers Ebooks distributes information supplied by third parties and provides links and references gathered from outside sources of The Web. By using this service, you agree to assume all risk of loss due to the use, which may be obtained by using this web site.

While visiting PDF All Designers Ebooks you can be sure that our site doesn't collect and store any personal information, but from time to time we can collect the information you browser contains: your IP address, type of your browser, what URL you have used and when. This information is used only with the purpose to improve the quality of our site and level of the services we offer. We want to admit that sometimes we can share the collected information with some third-parties, but just to help them to make our site even better. For example, if there is a group of users looking for a specific book or clicking the same advertising proposition, we can collect and share this information with third-parties to create targeting advertising or to offer these users more similar books to read. We strictly follow to all laws on personal information safety to protect our right and the safety of our users data.

PDF All Designers Ebooks produce automated search results like Google and every search may return unexpected or unwanted references. These references may contain offensive, obscene, or illegal material. PDF All Designers Ebooks just links to ( AND NOT IN ANY WAY PUBLISH!) content supplied by third parties or generally available on the Internet, PDF All Designers Ebooks has no more editorial control over such information than does a public library, bookstore, or newsstand. Any information, opinion, advice, statement, service, offer, or other materials or content are the property and responsibility of their respective author(s) or distributor(s) and NOT of PDF All Designers Ebooks.

The privacy of our visitors to PDF All Designers Ebooks is important to us. At PDF All Designers Ebooks, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit PDF All Designers Ebooks, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Safari, Google Chrome, or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on PDF All Designers Ebooks to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting").

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting New York, you may see New York hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information".

A snippet from Google Adsense Website:

"Google uses the DoubleClick cookie on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. Subject to any applicable laws, rules and regulations, you will have the sole and exclusive right to use all data derived from your use of the DoubleClick cookie for any purpose related to your business, provided that Google may use and disclose this data subject to the terms of [Google's advertising privacy policies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html "Google's advertising privacy policies") and any applicable laws, rules and regulations."

It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting **[this link](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx "Opt-out Ad Serving")**.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Online Books Libraries has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

Send the infringement notice via contact form with "DMCA Complaint" as your subject line otherwise we won't be able to process your complaint.

For PDF All Designers Ebooks DMCA Complaint, Please allow up to a week for an email response. Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due to the complaint not being filed properly.
